(Raj:)Now him, he's one of those geeks.
(Sheldon:)All right, now before you enter
my bedroom unescorted...
(Sheldon:)...I need you to understand
that this one time grant of access...
(Sheldon:)...does not create a permanent easement.
(Sheldon:)Easement.
It's a legal right of access. Good grief.
What? No, don't put me on hold. I...
Oh...
HOWARD:
Do you believe him?
(Howard:)Normally around women,
he has the personality of a boiled potato.
(Howard:)Put one beer in him,
and he's M. Knight Charmalarmalon.
(Leonard:)Is that what he's drinking?
It's not even real beer.
(Penny:)- What?
- Look at it.
(Leonard:)Non-alcoholic beer.
- Then what's going on?
- I don't know.
(Leonard:)Some sort of placebo effect, I guess.
(Howard:)Placebo, you say.
(Sheldon:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)Yes, I'm still here.
Where am I going? I'm on a train.